[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "What is your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "We don't really know I guess at the moment exactly what has happened here, do we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Your girlfriend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Where is she now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Outside with the police.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "I just want everyone to know the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "What can we deduce from this case, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Well, we know that, Piers, this past Monday, he was brought to an emergency room in order to be evaluated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Virginia"]}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "That is a shocking breakdown in the system, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "It is a shocking breakdown in the system and from the research I've done, Virginia has had the highest suicide rate in the past 13 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Why is that in fact in many states being reduced?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well a part of it is because a lot people see mental health care as being some sort of a luxury.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Does it not make it difficult if the word that is apparently so offensive is in common parlance amongst the group who say they find it offensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "I think it's ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Is he wise to continue using these deeply offensive words even in those communities?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I think that there is something when you said for reclaiming language.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "If you call me a queer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "IN", "IN", "WP", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "But you would continue to use that word about yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "That defined myself because of the history, because of what I've been through, because of what queer brothers and sisters been through.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Do you agree with that Don?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Nothing offense me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Don?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "You didn't know presumably the sexuality of this guy or was he just being angry and defensive thinking of the first that came into his head which is what I suspect was the case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "But is it homophobic or he just use homophobic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "It is biased.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alec Baldwin"]}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Is it right that he becomes the standard bearer of homophobic bigotry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "I don't know if the gay community has reasoned up against Alec Baldwin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "I don't think I'm even remotely offended but, you know, should I be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "In terms of you're own bipolar condition, when did you first realize that's what it was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "When I was about 14.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "But was that exacerbated, do you think, by the drug taken?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VB", ",", "``", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Did it help you become a great actor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Probably and I had lived from thrill to thrill and I had a certainty about my success which I can look back now and say, \"That was probably part of my manic.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Are you married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I am divorced.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Neil Diamond"]}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Would you like to talk about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "There are two types of people in this world, those who like Neil Diamond and those who don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "You think you can play a psychiatrist in real life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Absolutely, I can play anyone with a college education even though I didn't have one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "You can study over people do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Take us to significant issues at the moment, one ObamaCare, obviously been a hell of a mess the rollout, what do you make of that and you think they'll fix it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Well, I think for about 100 years one of the political parties has always tried to get a safety net under people and the other party hasn't, and now we have which is an enormous accomplishment and it started with glitches and problems, but I love to remind people that all of our national endeavor started out badly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA", "NRA"]}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "ORGAN: And in terms of the other issue which is the power of the NRA over the gun debate the apparent entrance (ph) of Washington to do anything about that, what is the root through that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Well, first of all I don't think the NRA is a villain, and I don't think that the people against the NRA are villains, I believe that's a problem of the press which started with an us-them problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"], "LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "When you yourself see that famous footage, that infamous footage, what goes through your mind even now, 50 years later?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Well, about the only thing I can think of is a I was hoping to save my prisoner and I didn't do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "In that moment, what was going through your mind as he burst through that group of people and came at you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Well, you don't have time to think about anything like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["J.D. Tippit"]}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "How did he come over to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "When I began talking with him, of course, I didn't -- I was talking to him about the murder of officer J.D. Tippit and that time I didn't have clue that he was going to be a suspect in the presidential shooting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What do you think about all the conspiracy theories given all the research that you've now done into this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I agree with my grandpa and the detective in my show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "``", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "In what stage before he was shot, did you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Capturing (inaudible), I just came back from the school book depository wherein they had found the riffle and they meet the hole around in the window and so forth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]